let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What Is Taylor Swifts Birthday?",
    answer: "Dec 13 1989",
    options: [
      "Oct 13 1989",
      "Dec 13 1989",
      "Dec 27 1989",
      "Jan 13 1989",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many pets does Taylor have?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is Taylor Swifts most popular song?",
    answer: "Cruel Summer",
    options: [
      "Cruel Summer",
      "I Dont wanna live forver",
      "You Belong With Me",
      "Blank Space",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is Taylor Swift's least streamed song?",
    answer: "All You Had To Do Was Stay - Commentary",
    options: [
      "New Year's Day - Karaoke Version",
      "Shake It Off - Commentary",
      "All You Had To Do Was Stay - Commentary",
      "King Of My Heart - Karaoke Version",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who is Taylor's current Boyfriend?",
    answer: "Travis Kelce",
    options: [
      "Joe Alwyn",
      "Travis Kelce",
      "Jake Gyllenhaal",
      "Travis Kelcee",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What song is this lyric found in: Never Take Advice from someone, whos, falling apart?",
    answer: "Dear Reader",
    options: [
      "Mastermind",
      "loml",
      "The Black Dog",
      "Dear Reader",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "What song is this lyric found in: a goddamn blaze in the dark?",
      answer: "Ivy",
      options: [
        "Cowboy Like Me",
        "Champagne Problems",
        "Ivy",
        "Willow",
      ]
    },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What album has the least amount of songs",
    answer: "Debut",
    options: [
      "Speak Now",
      "Fearless",
      "Reputation",
      "Debut",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "When did the Eras tour begin?",
    answer: "March 17, 2023",
    options: [
      "March 16, 2023",
      "March 17, 2023",
      "March 18, 2023",
      "March 19, 2023",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What year did Taylor Win her first Grammy?",
    answer: "2010",
    options: [
      "2007",
      "2008",
      "2009",
      "2010",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How old was Taylor when she won her first Grammy?",
    answer: "20",
    options: [
      "20",
      "21",
      "22",
      "23",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: painting pictures in the sky?",
    answer: "I'm only me when I'm with you",
    options: [
      "Picture to Burn",
      "I'm only me when I'm with you",
      "Fearless",
      "White Horse",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: until the day I die?",
    answer: "No Body No Crime",
    options: [
      "Evermore",
      "Cowboy Like Me",
      "No Body No Crime",
      "Willow",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: trying hard not to look like I'm trying?",
    answer: "Electric touch",
    options: [
      "Sparks fly",
      "Speak now",
      "Dear John",
      "Electric touch",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: this godforsaken mess that you made me?",
    answer: "Illicit affairs",
    options: [
      "Illicite affairs",
      "Seven",
      "This is me trying",
      "August",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: snakes and stones never broke my bones?",
    answer: "You Need To Calm Down",
    options: [
      "False God",
      "You Need To Calm Down",
      "Daylight",
      "AfterGlow",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: spinning out of control?",
    answer: "Wonderland",
    options: [
      "Say Don't Go",
      "Now That We Don't Talk",
      "Wonderland",
      "Is It Over Now",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: Hang your head low?",
    answer: "Cruel Summer",
    options: [
      "Cruel Summer",
      "All Of The Girls You Loved Before",
      "London Boy",
      "I Think He Knows",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: Donâ€™t read the last page?",
    answer: "New Years Day",
    options: [
      "Call it what you want",
      "New Years Day",
      "Delicate",
      "So it Goes",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: chains around my demons?",
    answer: "Invisble String",
    options: [
      "Hoax",
      "the 1",
      "illicit affairs",
      "Invisble String",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: you just see right through me?",
    answer: "Invisible",
    options: [
      "Invisible",
      "Picture to Burn",
      "Tim McGraw",
      "Should've Said No",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: one prize I'd cheat to win?",
    answer: "Willow",
    options: [
      "Evermore",
      "Dorthea",
      "Willow",
      "Closure",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: use my best colors for your portrait?",
    answer: "Tolerate It",
    options: [
      "Tolerate It",
      "The Archer",
      "Betty",
      "Snow on the Beach",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: Same old tired, lonely place?",
    answer: "Enchanted",
    options: [
      "Enchanted",
      "Last Kiss",
      "Ours",
      "Sparks Fly",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: I could go back to every laugh, but I don't wanna go there anymore?",
    answer: "Come in with the rain",
    options: [
      "Come in with the rain",
      "Mean",
      "Hey Stephan",
      "Ours"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "What song is this lyric from:I'd like to hang out with you for my whole life.",
    answer: "Stay Stay Stay",
    options: [
      "The Moment I Knew",
      "Stay Stay Stay",
      "The Last Time",
      "I Wish You Would",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: People like you always want back the love they gave away.",
    answer: "All you had to do was stay",
    options: [
      "New Romantics",
      "Wonderland",
      "You are in love",
      "All you had to do was stay",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "what song is this lyric from: I left a note on the door with a joke we'd made.",
    answer: "Holy Ground",
    options: [
      "State of grace",
      "Holy Ground",
      "Babe",
      "Forever Winter",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "What song is this lyric from: It's okay, life is a tough crowd.",
    answer: "Innocent",
    options: [
      "Innocent",
      "Timeless",
      "Better than Revenge",
      "Last Kiss",
    ]
  },
  
];

